Benjamin Rosati

WEB DESIGNER BENROSATI.COM

The digital products which I've had the opportunity to collaborate on have cultivated truly unique experiences for my ongoing practice. My approach comes from an authentic, enthusiastic, and passionate place, which focuses on designing genuine marketing material and developing engaging, successful campaigns.

EXPERIENCE

Independent Services

Web Design & Development | 2014 - Current

I provide ongoing design and development work for a dozen retainers on a contractual basis. I also manage one primary design & development contract at a time on more of a full-time basis which provides clientele with an experience similar to having an "in-house" on-call worker. All of these contracts have continued service with me on an as-need basis.

Design Rangers

Web Design & Development | 2012 – 2014

Worked alongside lead designers and developers in an agency environment to deliver bespoke, thoughtful designs to clients in a full spectrum of industries.

Ignition Interactive

Web Design & Development | 2010 – 2012

Worked alongside lead designers and developers in an agency environment to deliver bespoke, thoughtful designs to clients in a full spectrum of industries.

EDUCATION

School of Visual Arts (NYC)

Computer Art | 2008 – 2010

KEY CLIENTS INCLUDE

Advanced Educational Technologies Labs UX // UI // CODE

Springfield Water & Sewer Commission UX // UI // CODE

Center for International Studies Abroad UX // UI // CODE

Global Educators Ux // UI // CODE

Open Path Collective ux // ui // code

Green Collar Mass Save ux // ui // CODE

Emergeast UX // UI // CODE

Magic of Persia UX // UI // CODE

Torn Banner Games UX // UI // CODE

Skittles ui // code

Colorado Springs Give Campaign ART

Hunger Games Capitol Couture UX // UI

WB Scribblenauts Remix UX // UI

WB Happy Feet 2 Ux // UI

E! Ice Loves Coco ux // ui // code

E! Kourtney & Kim Take New York UX // UI // CODE

HBO Lady Gaga Monster Ball Tour UX // UI

HBO Boardwalk Empire UX // UI

Cinemax Femme Fatales UX // UI

LionsGate Films Warrior UX // UI

LionsGate Films Another Earth UX // UI

CAPABILITIES SOFTWARE **DEVELOPMENT** SOFT SKILLS Wireframing Adobe Photoshop HTML5 **Project Management** User Experience Design (UX) CSS3 Waterfall Approach Adobe Illustrator User Interface Design (UI) Adobe XD Sass Agile Approach Branding **Adobe Animate** Javascript Kanban Boards **Adobe After Effects Design Reviews** Logo jQuery **Art Direction Affinity Designer** PHP **Design Audits** Consultations **Graphic Design Affinity Photo** Wordpress Art Lead Web Design Figma Gulp Webflow Interactive Design